© anoXmous
@ https://thepiratebay.se/user/anoXmous
[Girl] "I'll miss you, Chihiro.
Your best friend, Rumi."
[Man] Chihiro.
Chihiro, we're almost there.
[Woman] This really is in
the middle of nowhere.
I'm gonna have to
go to the next town to shop.
We'll just have to learn to like it.
Look, Chihiro, there's your new school.
Looks great, doesn't it?
[Woman]
It doesn't look so bad.
It's gonna stink.
I liked my old school.
Mom! My flowers are dying.
I told you not to
smother them like that.
We'll put them in water
when we get to our new home.
I finally get a bouquet, and it's
a good-bye present. That's depressing.
Daddy bought you a rose for
your birthday. Don't you remember?
Yeah, one.
Just one rose isn't a bouquet.
Hold on to your card.
I'm opening the window.
And quit whining.
It's fun to move to a new place.
It's an adventure.
Wait. Did I take the wrong turn?
This can't be right.
- Look, there's our house.
- Huh?
[Mother]
It's that blue one on the end.
Oh, you're right.
I must have missed the turnoff.
This road should get us there.
[Mother] Don't take a shortcut.
You always get us lost.
- Trust me. It's gonna work.
- [Chihiro] What are those stones?
- They look like little houses.
- They're shrines.
Some people think
little spirits live there.
- Dad, I think we're lost.
- We're fine. I've got four-wheel drive.
- Sit down, please, sweetie.
- [Mother] Honey! Honey!
- Slow down! You're gonna kill us.
What's that?
- What's this old building?
- It looks like an entrance.
Honey, get back in the car.
We're going to be late.
Chihiro.
Oh, for heaven's sake.
This building's not old. It's fake.
These stones are
just made of plaster.
- The wind's pulling us in.
- What is it?
- Let's go in. I want to see
what's on the other side.
I'm not going.
It gives me the creeps.
Don't be such
a scaredy-cat, Chihiro.
- Let's just take a look.
- The movers will get to
our house before we do.
It's all right. They've got the keys.
They can start without us.
- All right. Just a quick look.
- Forget it. I'm not going.
Come on, you guys.
Let's get out of here.
Come on, honey. It'll be fun.
I'm not going!
Chihiro, just wait in the car then.
But, Mom!
- Wait for me!
Everybody, watch your step.
Chihiro, don't cling like that.
You'll make me trip.
What is this place?
- Oh, do you hear that?
- It sounds like a train.
- We must be near a train station.
Come on. Let's go check it out.
- What are those weird buildings?
- I knew it.
It's an abandoned theme park. See?
They built them
everywhere in the early '90s.
Then the economy went bad,
and they all went bankrupt.
This must be one of them.
Where are you going?
You said just a quick look.
Now let's go back.
Hey!
Did you hear that building?
It was moaning.
It's just the wind.
Oh, what a beautiful place.
We should have brought our lunch.
We could have had a picnic.
Look. They were planning
to put a river here.
Hmm?
- Hey, you smell that?
- Something smells delicious.
- Yeah, and I'm starving.
Maybe this theme park's
still in business. Let's go.
Chihiro, hurry it up.
Wait a minute.
Hmm.
Over there.
This way.
How strange.
They're all restaurants.
Where is everybody?
Ah, there it is.
Hey, I found it!
Hey, you gotta see this. In here.
Ahh, look at this.
Hello in there!
Does anybody work here?
- Come in, Chihiro. It looks delicious.
- Mm-mmm.
Anybody?
Don't worry, honey. We can pay the bill
when they get back.
Good plan. Hey, that looks great.
I wonder what this is called.
Oh, it's delicious. Chihiro,
you have to taste this.
I don't want any. We're gonna get
in trouble. Let's just get out of here.
Don't worry.
You've got Daddy here.
He's got credit cards and cash.
Mmm.
- Chihiro, you have to
try this. It's so tender.
- Mm-mmm.
- Mustard?
- Thank you.
- [Mother] Mmm.
Come on, you guys. You can't.
That's weird.
[Chihiro]
It's a bathhouse.
There's the train.
- You shouldn't be here.
Get out of here now!
- What?
- It's almost night.
Leave, before it gets dark.
They're lighting the lamps.
Get out of here.
You've gotta get across the river. Go!
I'll distract them.
What's up with him?
Mom! Dad!
Come on! Quit eating.
Let's get out of here!
Mom! Dad! Where are you?
Mommy!
Water?
What?
I'm dreaming!
Come on. Wake up! Wake up!
Wake up.
It's just a dream.
It's just a dream. Go away.
Away. Disappear.
I'm see-through!
It's just a bad dream.
- Oh!
[Woman]
You're thriving. Ah, yes.
- Looking forward to a relaxing time.
- Quite a long journey.
- [Woman] I hope they have...
Don't be afraid.
I just want to help you.
No! No! No!
Open your mouth and eat this.
You have to eat some food from
this world, or else you'll disappear.
No!
Don't worry.
It won't turn you into a pig.
- Chew it and swallow.
There you go. You're all better.
See for yourself.
- I'm okay.
- You see?
- Now, come with me.
- Where are my mom and dad?
They... didn't really
turn into pigs, did they?
You can't see them now,
but you will.
- Don't move.
That bird's looking for you.
You've gotta get out of here.
My legs! I can't stand up.
Help! What do I do?
Calm down.
Take a deep breath.
In the name of the wind
and water within thee, unbind her.
- Get up.
- [Man] Welcome. Welcome.
Always nice to see you.
Welcome back.
- Welcome. Welcome.
[Man]
You have to hold your breath
while we cross the bridge.
Even the tiniest breath will break the
spell, and then everyone will see you.
- [Man] Wonderful to see you.
- [Woman] Nice to see you.
- Welcome back.
I'm scared.
Now just stay calm.
Welcome. Welcome.
Always nice to see you.
Welcome back.
Welcome. Welcome.
- I'm back from my mission.
- Ahh, welcome.
Welcome back, Master Haku.
- Take a deep breath.
Hold it.
Welcome. Welcome.
Welcome back.
Good to see you.
- Hang on. Almost there.
Master Haku!
Where have you been?
Wha... A human?
Let's go!
Huh? Huh? Huh?
Master Haku!
[Man] Hurry. Boy, boy, boy,
it stinks up the place.
- They know you're here.
- I'm sorry. I took a breath.
No, Chihiro, you did very well.
Listen carefully to
what I tell you to do.
You can't stay here.
They'll find you...
and you'll never get
to rescue your parents.
I'll create a diversion
while you escape.
No! Don't leave me.
I don't wanna be alone.
You don't have any choice if you want
to help your parents.
This is what you have to do.
They did turn into pigs.
I wasn't dreaming.
Don't worry.
[Haku Narrating]
Now, when things quiet down,
go out through the back gate.
Go all the way down the stairs
until you reach the boiler room...
where they stoke the fires.
There you'll find Kamajii,
the boiler man.
Kamajii?
Tell him you want to work here.
Even if he refuses, you must insist.
If you don't get a job,
Yubaba will turn you into an animal.
Yubaba. Huh?
You'll see. She's the witch who
rules the bathhouse.
Kamajii will try to turn you away
or trick you into leaving...
but just keep asking for work.
It'll be hard work,
but you'll be able to stay here.
- Then, even Yubaba can't harm you.
- Mm-hmm.
- Master Haku?
- Master Haku, where are you?
I have to go. Don't forget, Chihiro,
I'm your friend.
How did you know
my name's Chihiro?
I've known you
since you were very small.
Good luck, and whatever you do,
don't make a sound.
- [Man] Master Haku.
Calm down. I'm coming.
[Man] Master Haku,
Yubaba wants to see you.
I know. It's about
my mission, right?
There's a human someplace.
We must find him.
Let's go this way.
Wait for me.
Wait for me. Wait.
Come on. Everything's fine.
Uh, hello. Excuse me.
Uh, hello?
Uh, hello. Are you Kamajii?
Eh?
Huh?
Haku told me to come here
and ask you for work.
- Could you give me a job?
Four bath tokens at once.
- Come on. Get to work, you little runts.
Yeah, I'm Kamajii...
slave to the boiler
that heats the baths.
Move it, ya stupid soot balls.
Please, I've gotta get a job here.
I don't need any help.
The place is full of soot.
I just cast a spell on them...
and I've got all
the workers I need.
- Oh. Sorry.
Wait. Just a second.
- Out of the way.
What should I do with this?
Should I leave it here?
Finish what you started, human.
- Hmm?
Hey, you runts. You wanna turn
back into soot?
And you, back off. You can't just take
someone else's job.
If they don't work, the spell wears off.
They turn back into soot.
There's no work for you here, got it?
Try somewhere else.
You soot balls got a problem?
Get back to work!
Chow time. What's going on?
Are you guys fighting again?
- Where's your other bowl?
- Oh. Ahh.
- From yesterday?
I keep telling you
to leave it out, Kamajii.
Meal time! Take a break.
A human! You're in trouble.
You're the one everyone's looking for.
- She's my granddaughter.
- Granddaughter?
She said she wants to work here...
but I've got all the help I need.
Will you take her to see Yubaba?
She's a tough little girl.
I think she can handle it.
No way.
I'm not gonna risk my life.
What if I give you
this roasted newt? Hmm?
It's a good one.
If you want a job, you'll have to
make a deal with Yubaba.
She's the head honcho here.
Give me that! Come on, little girl.
You better follow me.
- Can't you even manage a
"Yes, ma'am" or a "Thank you"?
- Yes, ma'am.
What a dope. Hurry up.
You don't need
your shoes or your socks.
- Just leave 'em.
- Yes, ma'am.
Thank the boiler man, you idiot.
You know, he's really sticking
his neck out for you.
Thank you, Mr. Boiler Man.
Good luck.
We have to go all the way to the
top floor. That's where Yubaba lives.
Get over here.
- You wanna lose your nose?
[Man]
More appetizers.
[Man #2]
Not spicy enough.
- We're halfway there. Just stay close.
- Okay.
Here we go.
The radish spirit.
Sorry, sir. This elevator
doesn't go any higher.
You'll have to take
another one. Thank you.
- He's following us.
- Just don't look at him.
- Step out to the right,
please, gentlemen.
I don't think they're big enough.
Your rooms are right this way.
- Hmm. Rin?
- What?
What's that smell?
- It's human. You smell
just like a human.
- Oh, really?
Where's it coming from, Rin?
Come on.
You're hiding something, aren't you?
- Show it to me.
- Is this what you smell?
Roasted... newt!
No way, frog.
I'm saving every last bite for myself.
Please, just a little bit.
Just give me a leg.
- If you wanna go up,
pull the lever on your right.
[Frog]
Gimme, gimme, gimme.
How could you be so cruel?
- [Frog] Can't you share?
Let me suck on the tail. Please!
- Let me...
- Mmm.
- Aren't you even going to knock?
You're the most pathetic little girl
I've ever seen.
Well, come in.
- I said, come in.
Quiet down.
You're making a racket.
Excuse me. I was wondering
if you could give me a job?
I don't want to hear
such a stupid request.
You're just a stinking,
useless weakling.
And this is certainly
no place for humans.
It's a bathhouse for the spirits.
It's where they come
to replenish themselves.
And you humans
always make a mess of things.
Like your parents, who gobbled up
the food of the spirits like pigs.
They got what they deserved,
and you should be punished too.
Hmm.
You could be a piglet.
Or, maybe you'd prefer
a lump of coal?
I can see you shaking. Actually,
I'm impressed you made it this far.
But I'm sure
you didn't do it on your own.
Let's thank whoever helped you.
Just who was it, dear?
Why don't you tell me.
- Please! Can't you give me a job?
- Don't start that again.
- Please, I just want to work.
Don't say that!
Why in world do you think
I should give you a job?
Anyone can see you're
a lazy, spoiled crybaby...
and you have no manners.
This is a high-class place
I'm running here.
So there's no job for you.
Now get out. I've got
all the lazy bums I need.
- Or maybe I'll give you the most
difficult job I've got...
and work you until you breathe...
your very last breath.
Oh, dear,
you woke up the baby.
Mommy's here.
Be a good boy now.
Why are you still here?
I told you to leave.
I want you to give me a job, please!
Quiet down! You're scaring the baby.
- Ooh! Hi, sweetie. Don't be angry.
- That's a good boy.
I'm not leaving
till you give me a job.
- Okay. Okay. Just be quiet.
Here comes Mommy.
I'm coming to get you.
That's your contract.
Sign your name away,
and I'll put you to work.
If I hear one little
complaint out of you...
you'll be joining
your parents in the pigpen.
So I...
Do I sign my name here?
Just sign it.
Do you want the job or not?
- I can't believe I took that oath.
Give a job to anyone who asks.
Ridiculous. I hate being
so nice all the time. Ha!
Are you done yet?
- So, your name's Chihiro.
- Yes, ma'am.
What a pretty name.
And it belongs to me now.
From now on, your name is Sen.
You got that?
- Answer me, Sen!
- Yes, ma'am.
You called for me?
This girl signed a contract.
Set her up with a job.
Right. What's your name?
What? Chih... Oh. It's Sen.
Okay, Sen. Follow me.
Haku, uh...
Don't talk to me,
and address me as Master Haku.
- I don't care if Yubaba
gets angry with us.
- We're not taking humans.
- She's already under contract.
- What?
- I promise to work very hard.
- We are not gonna
take her in our department.
- She'll stink up the whole place.
- We don't want her.
Three days of eating our food,
and her smell will go away.
If she doesn't work hard, roast her,
boil her, do whatever you want.
Now get back to work.
Where is Rin?
What? Don't you dump her on me.
- You said you wanted an assistant.
- That's perfect.
- Give the girl to Rin.
- Oh, great.
- Sen, get going.
- Right.
Why are you picking on me?
You owe me one, Haku. You hear me?
- Have a nice day.
- Hmph.
Come on.
I can't believe you pulled it off.
- Huh?
- You're such a dope.
I was really worried.
Now, keep on your toes,
and if you need anything, ask me. Okay?
- Okay.
- Hmm? What's wrong?
I don't feel so good.
So, this is our room.
A little food and some sleep
and you'll be fine.
Here's your apron. You have to
wash it yourself. Your pants.
You're so puny.
Way too big.
- Rin, you know Haku?
- What about him?
There aren't two of him
here, are there?
Two Hakus?
I can barely stand one. Too big.
He's Yubaba's henchman.
Don't trust anything he says.
- Let's see.
Ah, here we go.
Wh-What's wrong with you?
Are you feeling okay?
Quiet down. What's your problem?
It's the new girl.
She doesn't feel so good.
Meet me at the bridge.
I'll take you to your parents.
- My shoes are gone.
- Huh?
Thank you.
- Follow me.
We don't have much time.
If you're found here, you'll be
turned into a pig yourself.
- You must never come here
without me. Understand?
I understand.
Mom, Dad, are you all right?
It's me, Sen. Hey, wake up!
Mom! Dad!
What's wrong with them?
Are they sick?
No. They ate too much.
They're sleeping it off.
They don't remember
being human.
So look hard. It's up to you
to remember which ones they are.
Don't you worry, I promise
I'll get you out of here.
So just don't get any fatter
or they'll eat you!
Here are your clothes. Hide them.
- I thought they'd been thrown away.
- You'll need them to get home.
My good-bye card's still here.
Chihiro. Chihiro.
That's my name, isn't it?
That's how Yubaba controls you...
by stealing your name.
So hold on to that card.
Keep it hidden.
While you're here,
you must call yourself Sen.
I can't believe I forgot my name.
She almost took it from me.
If you completely forget it,
you'll never find your way home.
I've tried everything
to remember mine.
You can't remember your name?
No. But for some reason,
I remember yours.
Here you go. Eat this.
You must be hungry.
- No.
- I put a spell on it so it'll
give you back your strength.
Just eat it.
Have some more. You'll be all right.
[Haku] I've got to go now.
I'll be back to help you soon.
- Just stay out of trouble.
- Thank you, Haku. You're a good friend.
Haku.
He's a dragon?
Huh?
- Where were you, Sen?
I was really worried.
- I'm sorry.
- Out of my way.
- Gee, Sen...
haven't you ever worked
a day in your life?
- Rin and Sen, you get the big tub today.
- What?
- Hey, that's frog work.
- Orders from the top.
So quit your complaining.
Hello. Aren't you
getting wet out there?
- [Rin] Sen, hurry up.
- Coming.
I'll leave the door open for you.
- Heard you got the big tub, Rin.
- Leave me alone.
Those jerks. They haven't cleaned
this tub in months.
We only use this tub
for our really filthy guests.
Disgusting. This sludge is so caked on,
it'll take days to scrub off.
Rin, Sen, you've got
some customers on the way.
Wait! Give us a minute.
This is clearly harassment.
We'll have to soak it off. Get an herbal
soak token from the foreman.
A what?
- An herbal soak token.
- All right.
Hey, Rin, what's a foreman?
Hmm. Something's coming.
I wonder what?
What useless scum
is sleeking around in the rain?
I can't waste a token on you.
Relax. Good morning.
Enjoy. Have a nice bath.
- For the radish spirit.
- One sulfur soak.
Why are you still standing here?
Scrub it yourself.
I'm not giving you a token.
Relax. Good morning.
- I said scrub it yourself.
- But I was told it has
to have an herbal soak.
Well, that's too bad. Mugwort bath?
Relax and enjoy it.
- Hmm?
Foreman speaking. Oh, yes. What?
- Thank you very much.
- Get back here!
- Hey! Wait a minute.
- [Yubaba] What's going on?
- Nothing. Everything's fine.
- We have an intruder.
- Is it a human?
- I'm not quite sure.
Figure it out and report back.
Wow, Sen. You got a really good one.
Clip this on, then let go.
It goes straight to Kamajii,
then he sends us our water.
You pull on this to start
the water flowing. Give it a try.
- Uh, you're such a klutz.
- Yuck! What's in this water?
Dried worm salt.
It's supposed to be good for you.
And with water this murky,
you can't see all the sludge in the tub.
Yank it again when the bath
is full, it'll stop.
You can let go of the rope now.
I'll get us some breakfast.
Okay.
Ow!
Uh, sir.
The bath's not ready yet.
- There's so many.
- What? They're all for me?
- Uh... Uh...
Thanks, but I don't need any more.
- Uh...
- No. I only need one.
- Oh, Yubaba.
- It's a stink spirit.
- And apparently,
it's an extra smelly one.
- He's headed for the bridge.
We're closed.
Go away. We're not open.
- Go! Please, go. Leave us.
- There's no one here.
Hmm. Something's fishy.
That doesn't seem like
a stink spirit to me.
But we have no choice.
Go greet him.
Just give him a bath and get him
out of here as fast as you can.
Everybody go back to your rooms.
Back to your rooms.
- Don't worry about a thing.
Everybody just be calm.
- Sen, Yubaba wants to see you.
- Yes, sir.
- Sen, don't mess this up.
Take this guest to the big tub
and take care of him.
- But-But, I...
- No buts, or I'll turn you into coal.
- You hear me?
- It's here.
Hands down. You'll insult our guest.
Look about you, customer.
Welcome to our baths.
Oh, it's money.
- Sen, take the nice customer's money.
- Yes, ma'am.
Don't make him wait.
Get him to the bath.
This way.
- Get out of my way!
- Sen!
Our food!
Open your windows, all of them!
[Man]
Quickly!
What? Just a minute, sir.
Disgusting?
- I don't think it's very funny.
- Let's see what she'll do next.
Look. She wants to refill the tub.
Oh, dear! She's gonna waste
all our good water!
Ow!
Hmm. Who gave her
all the bath tokens?
Don't look at me. I didn't do it.
Oh, no! That's our best
herbal formula!
Sen! Sen, where are you?
Over here!
Don't worry.
St-Stay right where you are.
I'm coming to help you.
You're gonna be fine.
I won't let him hurt you.
I think he needs help. It feels like
there's a thorn in his side.
- A thorn?
- It won't come out!
What's that?
He has a thorn? Hmm.
- Get the staff down there. Step on it!
- Huh?
Right, right, right!
Get downstairs! Help her! You!
- All of you!
- Listen to me.
That's no stink spirit
we have on our hands...
- Grab onto this rope.
- Wait!
- Mmm. Hold on tight.
- Got it.
- Hurry up, now.
- Get in there!
Everyone get in there
and help them.
We've got it tied on!
Everyone, ready on my command.
And... heave!
[All]
- Heave!
- And...
- heave!
- Heave!
And heave!
A bicycle?
Thought so.
Get ready, now!
- Heave!
Heave!
Sen! Sen, where are you?
Well done.
Huh?
Ahh!
- Gold!
Hey, wait!
That's company property!
- Stop!
- Back off!
- Our guest is still here, you idiots!
Sen, you're in our guest's way.
Step aside.
- Yes, ma'am.
- Open the main gates! Make way!
Sen, you did great!
We made so much money!
That spirit is rich and powerful.
Everyone, learn from Sen.
- Sake's on the house tonight.
- But first, hand over
all the gold you picked up.
- That's not fair!
- How stingy! That's no fair!
Here.
- I swiped a dumpling for you.
- Thank you.
What a day. Mmm.
- Rin, have you seen Haku?
- Not Haku again.
He just disappears sometimes.
Rumor has it he runs around
doing Yubaba's dirty work.
- Does he really?
- [Woman] Lights out, Rin.
Fine.
There's so much water.
It looks like a sea.
What'd you expect
after all that rain?
I've gotta get out of this place.
Someday, I'm getting on that train.
Mmm.
- What's wrong?
Ah!
Hmm.
Uh-uh.
Huh?
Ahh!
It's gold! Huh?
What do you think you're doing?
You're not allowed in there.
The bath's closed.
Get out, you! Get out of there!
Ooh! Oh! More gold!
Are you... Are you...
Are you giving them to me?
Wait. You can make gold?
Ahh.
Uh, gimme!
What's going on in there?
It's way past bedtime. Come on!
-Wh...
Hey, boss, up here.
I'm hungry. Starving!
- And I want you to serve me.
- I know that voice.
Here, I'll pay you up front.
And... I wanna take a bath too.
Why don't you wake everyone up?
Mom, Dad, I got a gift
from the river spirit!
Maybe if you eat it,
it'll break the spell.
Which ones are you?
Mom, Dad!
Bad dream.
Rin?
Where is everybody?
Wow. It really is a sea.
There's Mom and Dad's pigpen.
I sure hope they're doing
all right over there.
Kamajii lit the boiler already?
How long was I asleep?
- Hurry up!
Come on, he's starving!
Can't you cook any faster?
Serve everything you've got,
even leftovers if you have to.
Hurry up! He's starving!
- Hey, Sen.
- Oh, Rin.
I was just coming
to wake you up. Look.
It's real gold.
There's a new guest here who's loaded.
He's giving gold away
by the handfuls!
Just keep the food coming.
I wanna eat everything!
Hmm. Who is the guest?
Oh, who cares? Come on,
before Yubaba wakes up.
I'm going to go look for Haku.
Oh! Would you quit
worrying about Haku?
- Come on, Sen. Let's go get some gold.
- Come on, Rin!
- Let's go get some more!
- You bet!
[Girl]
Hey, wait for me!
Where is Haku?
He better get here before I forget
what my parents look like.
I sure hope Dad hasn't gotten too fat.
Hmm?
Haku?
It's Haku! He's back!
Are birds chasing him?
Haku! Fight 'em! Come on!
He's hurt!
Haku, this way!
Aah!
Huh? It's just paper.
Haku, you're bleeding.
Hold still.
Those paper things are gone now.
You're going to be all right.
He went in that top window.
I've got to get there
before he bleeds to death!
# Welcome the rich man
He's hard for you to miss #
# His butt keeps getting bigger
so there's plenty there to kiss #
Oh, hey, everybody, bow down.
[All]
Welcome, rich man.
# Beg for tips
This is the time #
- # Beg for tips
Make yourselves a dime #
Give me some dough!
Give me some tips!
I'll do anything for you!
Just give me some tips!
- Hey, what are you doing?
- Going upstairs.
- No, you're not.
Huh? Aah! Blood!
Get out of the way!
Our guest is coming through here!
Thank you for helping me earlier.
- Don't talk to him, you stinking hum...
- Hey!
I don't want any, but thanks.
I'm sorry,
but I'm in a really big hurry.
- Hey, there! Hey!
Get back! Get back now!
- Ow!
Everybody, out!
Oh, I'm terribly sorry, sir.
You'll have to excuse the little girl.
She's just a human.
- Wipe that smile off your face.
- What?
- You're still smiling.
- No, I'm not.
Aah!
Huh?
It's Yubaba!
[Yubaba]
We're in a big mess.
I found out who
our rich customer is.
He's a No-Face!
It's all your fault. You're so greedy.
You attract terrible guests.
All right, I'm on my way.
Don't let him eat anyone else
till I get down there.
Haku is bleeding
all over the carpet.
Get him out of here.
He'll be dead soon anyway.
- Ahh.
Hi, sweetie.
Hiding under the cushions again?
Oh, I woke you,
and you were sound asleep.
I'm sorry.
Let me give you a kiss.
Go back to sleep, now.
Ow! Let go of me!
Wow, you're a big baby.
Would you mind letting go of me?
- I'm in a really big hurry.
- You came in here to make me sick.
- Huh?
- You're a bad germ from
outside, aren't you?
I'm not a germ, I'm a human.
Now, would you please let go of me?
You'll get sick if you go outside.
So stay here and play with me.
- You won't get sick.
- Yes, you will.
That's why I've never left this room.
Staying in this room
is what'll make you sick.
Listen, someone very important
to me is terribly hurt.
I've got to go right now,
so please let go of me.
If you go I'll cry,
and Mama will hear me...
and Mama will come in here and kill you.
- Play with me, or I'll break your arm.
- That hurts!
Please! I'll play with you later, okay?
- No, I wanna play now!
- Germs! I've got germs, see?
Haku!
What are you doing? Get away!
Get back! Haku, are you okay?
- Can you hear me?
- Shut your mouth! Haku!
- Get back!
Stop it!
I'm not afraid of germs.
If you don't play with me, I'll cry.
Please don't cry. Just wait.
Right now, or I'll start crying.
Don't cry! Don't cry!
What a spoiled brat!
Shut your big mouth!
You're a bit of a porker, aren't you?
- Hmm. Still see-through.
- Mama?
You pea-brain. Can't you even tell me
from your own mother?
There, now. Your body
matches your brain.
Let's see.
What else can we mess with?
This is our little secret.
You tell anyone else,
and I'll rip your mouth out.
- Who are you?
- Zaneba. I'm Yubaba's twin sister.
It was nice of you to lead me
straight to this dragon's hiding place.
Now, hand him over to me.
What do you want with Haku?
He's badly hurt.
Too bad. He stole my solid gold seal.
It's magic and powerful,
and I want it back!
Haku wouldn't steal.
He's a good person.
Huh! Do you know why he became
my sister's apprentice?
To steal her magic secrets,
and now he's stolen my magic too.
He's a greedy little thief.
There's nothing good about him.
Step aside, little girl.
I'm going to take my seal back from him.
There's a spell on the seal,
and anyone who steals it will die.
- No, you can't!
You idiots! What's your problem?
Keep quiet. I don't want my sister
coming up here.
Ow. A paper cut.
Haku, we're falling!
Haku!
- What's going on here?
Sen, be careful! Stay back!
- Haku!
Are you okay? Haku!
- What's wrong with you?
This looks serious.
Haku, don't give up!
What do we do? Is he dying?
It looks like he's bleeding
from the inside.
- From the inside?
- I think so.
Maybe he swallowed something.
Haku, I got this gift
from the river spirit.
Eat it. Maybe it'll help.
Come on! Open your mouth!
Please, Haku! Eat it!
See? It's okay.
Medicine from the river spirit.
Open your mouth. That's it.
Got it.
- Now swallow.
- Sen, look there!
- The gold seal!
- Get that black slug!
Over there! Get it!
Get it!
[Kamajii] You killed it?
Those things are bad luck.
Hurry, before it rubs off on you!
Put your thumbs
and forefingers together.
- Evil, be gone!
- Haku stole this seal
from Yubaba's sister.
Zaneba's solid gold
monogrammed seal.
That's as powerful as it gets.
Look! He's changed back.
Help me. What do we do?
- Haku! Haku, wake up!
Zaneba put a curse on the seal.
That's strong magic.
It's made him gravely ill.
That should make him
more comfortable.
Poor Haku. He's had it
hard ever since he got here.
He just showed up
out of nowhere, just like you did.
But he got mixed up with Yubaba.
He took a job as her apprentice.
I warned him it was too dangerous.
"Just quit.
Go back home, "I told him.
But he said for some reason
he had no home to return to.
Once Yubaba
got control over him...
his face turned pale
and his eyes turned steely.
- He's never been the same.
Kamajii, what if I take
the gold seal back to Zaneba?
I could give back the seal
and apologize to her for Haku.
Can you tell me
where Zaneba lives?
You'd go to Zaneba's?
- It might help, but she's
one dangerous witch.
- Please?
Haku helped me before.
Now I wanna help him.
Hmm.
I know how you can get there,
but you'll have to get back on your own.
Wait here.
Let's see, now. I know it's
around here somewhere.
Everyone, I need my shoes
and clothes, please.
I guess my parents will have to wait.
Sen! I've looked everywhere for you.
- Rin!
- There's blood everywhere.
What's going on here?
Who are those guys?
I picked up some new friends. See?
- Everyone's looking for you.
Yubaba is furious.
- Huh?
The guy with all the gold
turned out to be a monster
called "No-Face."
And he says that you
let him into the bathhouse.
I did let him in.
Are you serious?
Yeah. I thought he was a customer.
What? He's a monster.
He's already swallowed three people.
Found it! Here it is, Sen.
- Hey, we're busy, boiler man.
- You can use this.
You've got train tickets?
Uh, how did you get a hold of them?
I've been saving them
for 40 years.
Now, listen carefully. The train stop
you want is called Swamp Bottom.
- Swamp Bottom?
- That's where Zaneba lives.
- The sixth stop.
- Sixth stop.
Make sure you get it right.
The train used to run
in both directions...
but these days it's a one-way ride.
Still want to go?
Yep. I'll walk back along the tracks.
- Sen, what about No-Face?
- I'll take care of that now.
Haku, I'll be back soon.
Just hold on.
What's going on?
Something you wouldn't recognize.
It's called "love."
- He just keeps getting bigger!
- I'm scared.
- I don't wanna be eaten by it.
- It's her.
Oh, Sen, thank goodness.
Yubaba can't hold him off much longer.
[Yubaba]
There's no need to get upset.
- I'm sure they'll find Sen somewhere.
Where is Sen? I want Sen!
Hurry! This way!
- Madam, Sen is here now.
- Finally!
Sen has arrived, sir. She'll be
with you in just a few minutes.
- He's destroying everything.
It's costing us a fortune.
So suck up to him and get every last
speck of gold he's...
Ew! What's that dirty mouse doing here?
Huh? He's your...
He doesn't look familiar?
Familiar? Don't be stupid.
Now, get in there.
Here's Sen.
Will Sen be all right
in there by herself?
- You wanna take her place? Hmph!
- Huh?
Try this. It's delicious.
Want some gold? I'm not giving it
to anybody else.
Come closer, Sen.
What would you like?
Just name it.
I would like to leave, sir.
I have someplace
I need to go to right away, please.
You should go back
to where you came from.
Yubaba doesn't want you
in the bathhouse any longer.
Where is your home?
Don't you have any friends or family?
No. No!
I'm lonely.
What is it that you want?
I want Sen.
I want Sen!
Take the gold. Take it!
- Are you going to eat me?
- Take it!
- Ooh! Huh?
- Huh.
- Ow.
If you want to eat me,
eat this first.
I was saving this for my parents...
but I think you'd better have it.
- Sen!
Sen, what did you do to me?
Aah!
Enough! I don't care if he's rich!
This nonsense has gotta stop!
[Sen]
No-Face!
Over here!
Run for your life!
Now, that's an esophagus!
I'll get you for this, Sen!
Duck!
Excuse me.
Sen, this way!
Hey, over here!
Sen, don't call him over!
I think being in the bathhouse
makes him crazy.
He needs to get out of there.
- Yeah? And go where?
- I don't know.
You don't know? Great.
Now he's following us.
[Sen]
He won't hurt us.
Hmm?
- You'll have to walk from here.
- Okay.
The station's just down the tracks.
Thanks, Rin.
- You better come back, you hear me?
- I will.
Sen, I'm sorry I called you
a dope before! I take it back!
No-Face, if you put even one scratch
on that girl, you're in big trouble.
There's the station.
Here comes the train. Come on.
Oh. We'd like to go
to Swamp Bottom, please.
Huh?
- Oh. You wanna come with us?
- Uh-huh.
He'd like to come too, please.
Uh... Uh...
Sit here. Behave yourself, okay?
- Kamajii, wake up.
- Hmm?
- Haku, you're all right.
- I'm fine. Where is Sen?
Did she go somewhere?
Can you tell me what's going on?
You blacked out, remember?
Yeah, I remember being in darkness.
Then I could hear Sen's voice
calling out my name.
So I followed her voice,
and the next thing I knew...
I was lying here
feeling better than ever.
Pure love. It broke Zaneba's spell.
Sen left to return the golden seal.
She did it to save you.
[Yubaba]
This gold doesn't even come close...
to covering the damage
that stupid No-Face caused.
Sen didn't get nearly enough.
She'll have to be punished.
- Madam, you see, Sen was the one
that saved us from No-Face.
- Yes, yes.
So what?
This whole mess is her fault.
And now she's run away from here.
She's even abandoned
her own parents!
- Those pigs must be ready
to eat by now.
- Turn them into bacon.
- Wait a minute.
- Huh?
- Master Haku?
You're still alive?
What is it you want?
You still haven't noticed that something
precious to you has been replaced.
Don't get fresh with me, young man.
Since when do you talk
that way to your master?
Huh.
My baby!
No!
- My baby!
- It's just dirt.
Where's my baby?
Where are you, sweetie?
Come out! Please, come out!
Where are you?
Sweetie!
Sweetie pie!
You!
Where is he?
What did you do with my baby?
He's with your sister.
Zaneba?
Uh...
Very clever, Haku. I get it.
You'll get my baby back for me,
but at a price.
So, what do you want?
Tear up Sen's contract.
And then I want you to return
Sen and her mother and father
back to the human world.
Fine, but on one condition.
I get to give Sen one final test.
If she fails, she's mine.
I hope this is the right stop.
Let's go.
You can ride on my shoulder
if you're tired.
Hmm?
[Zaneba]
Come in.
Hello?
Hurry up. I don't have all day.
Come on.
- So, you all made it.
- Hmm?
Sit down. I'll make some tea.
Excuse me, ma'am. Haku stole this
from you. I came to give it back.
I see.
Do you have any idea what this is?
Yes. It's the golden seal
you were looking for.
I'm here to apologize for Haku.
I'm very sorry.
He sliced me in two, you know,
and I'm still angry.
- What?
- What? The protective spell is gone.
I'm sorry. You mean that black slug
that was on your seal?
I think I squashed it with my foot.
Squashed it?
That wasn't my slug.
My sister put that slug into Haku
so she could control him.
You squashed it.
What happened to my spell?
Only love can break it.
Come, now.
Can you please turn these two
back into their normal forms?
The spell on those two
wore off long ago.
Change back if you want.
I don't get along with my sister.
She's so obnoxious.
You saw how tacky her home is.
- We're identical twins,
yet exact opposites.
I'm sorry she turned
your parents into pigs.
But there's nothing I can do.
It's just the way things are.
You'll have to help your parents
and Haku on your own.
Use what you remember
about them.
What? Can't you please
give me more of a hint than that?
It seems like I met Haku before,
but it was a long time ago.
That's a good start.
Once you've met someone,
you never really forget them.
It just takes a while
for your memories to return.
While you're thinking, the boys
and I are going to make you something.
And I want you
to call me Granny from now on.
- Ah, come on. Keep at it.
No-Face, where did you
learn to spin thread?
You're really good at this.
Now let's weave
the threads together.
Knit one, pearl two.
Knit one... That's right.
Granny, I can't remember
anything at all.
Haku could be dead already,
and I'm just sitting around here.
My mom and dad could've
been eaten for dinner.
Wait just a little bit longer.
Ahh. There we go.
Use it to tie back your hair.
It's beautiful.
It'll protect you.
It's made from the threads
your friends wove together.
Thank you.
What good timing.
We've got another guest.
- Will you let him in?
- Sure.
Haku! Haku.
Thank goodness.
You're alive! I can't believe it.
How did it happen?
Ahh.
That's love for you.
Look, Granny. Haku's alive.
- Haku, I will forgive you
for stealing my precious seal.
But in return,
you must take care of this girl.
Okay, you two,
it's time to go home.
Come back soon.
No-Face,
why don't you stay with me?
- I could use a good helper.
Granny!
Thank you so much. I'll miss you.
Don't worry. You'll be all right, Sen.
I want you to know my real name.
It's Chihiro.
Chihiro. What a pretty name.
- You take good care of it.
- I will.
- Off you go.
- Okay. Bye.
Granny, take care!
Thanks for everything!
Haku, listen.
I just remembered something
from a long time ago.
I think it may help you.
Once, when I was little,
I dropped my shoe into a river.
And when I tried
to get it back, I fell in.
I thought I'd drown, but the water
carried me to shore.
It finally came back to me.
The river's name was
the Kalaku River.
I think that was you,
and your real name is Kalaku River!
You did it, Chihiro! I remember.
I was the spirit of the Kalaku River.
- A river spirit?
- My name is the Kalaku River.
They filled in that river.
It's all apartments now.
That must be why I can't
find my way home, Chihiro.
I remember you falling into my river,
and I remember your little pink shoe.
So you're the one who carried me back
into shallow water.
You saved me.
I knew you were good.
- Hey, there they are!
I see you failed
to bring my baby back.
- Mama!
- My baby!
Are you traumatized?
Did they do terrible things to you?
You're standing all by yourself.
When did that happen?
Don't forget your promise.
You must return Chihiro
and her parents to the human world.
Hmph! Not so fast, Haku.
I get to give Sen one final test.
- Shut up!
Stop it, Mama. Leave her alone.
- Sen and I had a really good time.
But a deal is a deal, sweetie.
I have to give Sen one final test.
If you make Sen cry,
I won't like you anymore.
- But... Granny?
- [Chihiro] Hey, Granny!
You're right. A deal's a deal.
Okay, I'm ready. I'll take your test.
Hmm. You've got guts.
I've got your contract right here.
Come this way.
This'll only take a minute.
Don't worry.
See if you can tell which of these pigs
is your mother and father.
You get one try.
If you get it right,
you can all go home.
Huh? There must be a mistake.
None of these pigs
are my mom or dad.
None of them?
Is that really your answer?
- Mm-hmm.
[All]
Oh, you got it!
Thank you, everyone.
All right, you win.
Get out of my sight.
Thanks for everything, Granny. Good-bye!
- [All] Good-bye!
- Thank you!
- Haku!
- Let's go!
- Where are my mom and dad?
- When you passed the test...
they woke up
on the human side of the river.
They're there now,
and they're looking for you.
There's no water here.
- I can walk across now.
- But I can't go any farther.
Just go back the way you came.
You'll be fine.
But you have to promise not to
look back, not until you've
passed through the tunnel.
What about you? What'll you do?
Don't worry. I'll go back
and have a talk with Yubaba.
I'll tell her I'm going
to quit being her apprentice.
I'm fine. I got my name back.
- Will we meet again sometime?
- Sure we will.
- Promise?
- Promise.
Now go, and don't look back.
- [Mother] Chihiro!
Where have you been?
Hurry up!
Mom, Dad!
- You shouldn't run off like that, honey.
- You could get in big trouble.
Are you guys sure you're all right?
[Mother] Let's go.
I don't wanna miss the movers.
Chihiro, hurry up.
Everybody, watch your step.
Chihiro, don't cling like that.
You'll make me trip.
We made it.
Hey, what happened?
What is it?
Look at that.
- It's all dusty inside too.
- Is this someone's idea of a joke?
- Looks like it.
- I told you we shouldn't have stopped.
[Mother] Come on, Chihiro.
Let's get to our new home.
[Father]
You're not scared, are you?
Don't be afraid, honey.
Everything's gonna be okay.
[Father] A new home and a new school?
It is a bit scary.
[Chihiro]
I think I can handle it.
© anoXmous
@ https://thepiratebay.se/user/anoXmous